<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Digital World</string>

    <!-- Strings Login -->
    <string name="txt_user">User</string>
    <string name="txt_password">Password</string>
    <string name="txt_login">Login</string>
    <string name="txt_sign_up">Sign Up</string>

    <!-- Strings Sign Up -->
    <string name="txt_first_name">First Name</string>
    <string name="etxt_first_name">You first name</string>
    <string name="txt_last_name">Last Name</string>
    <string name="etxt_last_name">You last name</string>
    <string name="txt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="etxt_email">You email</string>
    <string name="etxt_password_sign_up">You password</string>
    <string name="txt_terms">Terms of service</string>
    <string name="txt_user_registration">Create Account</string>
    <string name="txt_valid_password">Valid Password</string>
    <string name="txt_invalid_password">Invalid Password</string>

    <!-- Strings Sign Up -->
    <string name="txt_terms_title">Terms and Conditions Policy</string>
    <string name="txt_terms_activity">
        General terms and conditions of use of the Marketplace
        DIGITAL WORLD. is a commercial company domiciled in the Republic of Colombia that
        makes available on its website www.digitalworl.com/ ("The Site" or "digitalworld.com")
        a platform ("Marketplace"), which allows the exhibition and commercialization of goods
        and/or services ("the Products") by national or international sellers acting in their
        personal capacity and therefore independent from DIGITAL WORLD ("the Sellers"), for the
        online acquisition of the same by consumers ("Customers" or "Users").
        DIGITAL WORLD is therefore not a distributor of the Products offered by the Sellers, does
        not have any contractual position within the transaction made between Customers and Sellers,
        nor can it be qualified as a reseller of the products offered by the Sellers in the Marketplace.

        Scope of application of the Terms of Use
        The present general conditions of use of the Marketplace ("Conditions of Use") apply to all
        orders of Products made by the Users to the Sellers of the Marketplace. The applicable Terms of
        Use are those in force at the time the order is placed by the User. Likewise, the Seller by the
        mere fact of exhibiting the Products in the Marketplace confirms the understanding and
        unconditionally accepts the application of the same.

        Capacity to use the platform
        The services offered in the Marketplace may only be used by persons who have legal capacity to
        contract in accordance with the provisions of the Colombian legislation in force.

        Purchase Process
        The Users can order the Products offered in the Marketplace directly and independently by the
        Sellers, which can be clearly identified by a mark in the description of the same or by the
        expression "Sold by". The description of the Products is provided by the Sellers, who are
        therefore solely responsible for the completeness of the description provided and the conformity
        of the Products with such description.
        By clicking on the "Buy" icon during the order process, after having read the General Conditions
        of Sale and Return Policy of the Seller indicated at the end of the file of each Product, and
        having checked the content of the order or, if applicable, after the modification of the same,
        the User declares to accept fully and without reservation the entirety of the Conditions of Use
        of the Marketplace.

    </string>
    <string name="txt_terms_ok">OK</string>

    <!-- Strings Menu Navigation -->
    <string name="title_activity_menu">MenuActivity</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">Slideshow</string>


</resources>